Come on climb aboard Scholastic's The Magic
School Bus for even more wild rides! Now you
can collect all the fun and Scholastic's The Magic
School Bus video collection. Cool! With the Frizz,
Arnold, Wanda and the rest of the gang. Join
them for all of their exciting action-packed
adventures. Find out what happens when Arnold
swallows the bus in the Magic School Bus for
lunch. Check out what's making Ralphie sick in
the Magic School Bus inside Ralphie. Wow! When
the kids get trapped in a haunted house, they
never know what the next sound is going to be.
In the Magic School Bus in the haunted house.
Watch this! Experience the wonderful world of
animal habitats in the Magic School Bus hops
home. Make waves as the gang Journeys to the
ocean floor in the Magic School Bus gets eaten.
This is so cool! Blast Off on a field trip that's
out of this world when the Magic School
Bus Gets Lost in Space. Come along class!
Collect all of Scholastics The Magic School Bus
videos so they can become lasting additions to
your video library. I'd say it's a perfect
time for a field trip. come on on the magics
de
seat belts everyone please let this be
a normal field trip with a [ __ ] no way
cruising on down Main Street you're relaxed
and feeling good next thing that you know you
seeing octopus in my neighborhood surfing on
the sound wave swinging through the star take
a left at human testing pick your second right
past Mars on the magic school Navigator nostril
I'm on the Magic School bus SP PL magic school
drop the river of lava Magic School such a fine
thing to do so stop your to the seat come on in
and don't be shy just to make your day complete
you might get baked into a p mag step inside it's
a wild ride come on ride on the Magic School Bus
hey Rousy wait for
me W I can't move
W yes how's it going Liz aren't
you psyched the Friz is taking
us to the beach today don't forget we
can't go until after our reports then
let's keep the reports short da yep
where there's a will there's a way
we brought sand in a crab shell for our two
Beach things that go together report didn't
we Carlos wao a humongous wave at 10:00 see crabs
dig in the sand so crabs and sand go together wi
out what did you bring Ralphie ah
hello everyone hi you guys Phoebe
phoei did you bring the tun grass
Ralphie have I ever let you down did
you bring the sun actually I couldn't
fit it in my napsack but I did bring
this the sun in all its Glory at
my old school we weren't allowed
to bring the sun to class how about you
Tim check it out a stunning portrait of
the rock to go with Wanda's muscle you
did bring the muscle didn't you Wanda
taada one muscle to go with Tim's Rock I named
him gusle the muscle Gus for short who's Gus for
short hi Kesha Gus is the muscle I brought for
the two Beach things that go together at court
see oh no oh help oh bad oh bad bad oh bad bad
bad bad bad bad bad bad something wrong I totally
forgot about the report you did you didn't
bring anything thing just my swimsuit in a
towel and a tuna fish sandwich uhoh
what's wrong with that I love tuna
sandwiches listen don't panic yet who's
your partner Arnold don't worry Arnold
likes reports he probably did the
whole thing himself where is Arnold
anyway Arnold hi guys yuck what happened to
your shoe I was running and I sort of stepped
into the pond near our house and you were
running because you're in a hurry because
you couldn't wait to show me what you did for our
two Beach things to go together report right Mom
I knew I forgot something you mean you didn't
bring anything either just my bathing suit in
a towel and the scum on your shoe scum and
a tuna fish sandwich da what do we think of
that but do scum and a tuna fish sandwich go
together hey maybe they do think think think
think think think think no oh great not only
do I get slimed by Pawn scum but I forget my
report I knew I should have stayed home today hey
we can't just give up Arnold we have to work with
what we got but kha oh good morning class good
morning Miss prle we have an exciting day ahead
of us haven't we hang T you guys maybe she'll
forget the reports and the first thing on the
agenda is your two Beach things that go together
reports then again maybe she won't let's start
with um rfie and Phoebe why the Sun and dun grass
Go Together by us all rights reserved Doom grass
like other plants uses energy from the Sun to
make its own food no sun no Doom grass no sun no
nothing oh Kesha and Arnold why don't you
go next yes well um we brought this um
nutritious tuna fish sandwich and this
delightful green scum you did why that
is absolutely fantastic it is so tell us
what the connection is between delightful
green scum and a nutritious tuna fish
sandwich um uh um they both have um
adjectives oh oh dear hold that thought
it's time to go to the beach oh but don't
worry we'll finish your reports
when we get back line up by the
door please Saved by the Bell yeah I never
thought I'd be glad to go on a field trip
oh for once a nice peaceful day at the beach
forget it Arnold everyone else will have a
wonderful time but we've got work to do now
concentrate how does your scum go with my
sandwich you know class this trip just might give
you the answer you're looking for I wonder if
she knows we don't know she knows everything
well not exactly everything it's your job as
scientist to look for connections connections
you mean how things go together exactly
we're here everybody
out there's Doom grass with
the sun beaming down on
it and here's a rock covered with Gus's family
look at them all it's a regular Muscle Beach car